emmanuel.tv KIDS
Prophet T.B. Joshua with Children in South Korea
This is T.B. Joshua on one of his visits to South Korea enjoying the company of children.
They're singing and happy to be in the presence of someone they have seen God using mightily.
Prophet T.B. Joshua with Children in South Korea
This endearing scene reminds us of Matthew 19:14
where Jesus said, "Let the little children come to me.
Don't stop them for the kingdom of Heaven belongs to such as these".
Be an obedient child.
Obey your father and your mum.
Prophet T.B. Joshua with Children in South Korea.
Black!
Look at the action of this little boy.
He rubs Prophet T.B. Joshua's skin as if his colour would rub off.
We are uniquely created on the outside, but in our hearts we are made to be like Jesus.
I love you!
Even at the dinner table, the children are reluctant to leave the presence of the man of God.
They continue to play with him and admire what makes him different which is the grace of God.
emmanuel.tv KIDS